Finding Aid for St. Andrew’s Church (Saginaw, Mich.) records, 1862-1956
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
St. Andrew’s Church (Saginaw, Mich.) records 1862-1956
St. Andrew’s Church (Saginaw, Mich.).
2 microfilm reels
86936 mf 537c, mf 538c
Baptismal, marriage, death, and communion and confirmation records.
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
The records were made available for microfilming by the church (donor no. 7215 ).
No further additions to the records are expected.
The record group is closed except with the permission of the donor.
St. Andrew's Church was founded in 1852.
The record group consists of microfilm of church registers containing records of baptisms, communion and confirmations, marriages and burials. The records are closed to research except with the permission of the church.
Subjects:
Saginaw (Mich.); Catholic Church--Michigan--Saginaw.; St. Andrew's Church (Saginaw, Mich.)
- Church registers
  - Index to Baptismal Records (Reel 1)
  - Baptismal Records 1862-1935
    - September 7, 1862-May 13, 1894 (Reel 1)
      (also includes records of first communion and confirmation, 1874-1878 pp.718-711)
    - May 27, 1894-April 26, 1908 May 21-August 21, 1921 (Reel 1)
    - May 10, 1908-June 30, 1935 (Reel 1)
      (does not include May 21-August 21, 1921)
  - Registrum Matrimonii, 1862-1949
    - November 21, 1862-December 24, 1901 (Reel 1)
    - January 15, 1902-February 26, 1908 (Reel 1)
    - June 23, 1908-January 22, 1949 (Reel 2)
  - Registrum Defunctor, 1862-1956
    - November 25, 1862-January 17, 1902 (Reel 2)
      (also includes record of first communion and confirmation, 1880 and April 24, 1887-June 21, 1901)
    - June 12, 1902-November 12, 1956 (Reel 2)